[
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 0",
        "front": "佳",
        "back": "아름다울 가"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 1",
        "front": "鳴",
        "back": "울 명"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 2",
        "front": "望",
        "back": "바랄 망"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 3",
        "front": "恕",
        "back": "용서할 서"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 4",
        "front": "池",
        "back": "못 지"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 5",
        "front": "捕",
        "back": "잡을 포"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 6",
        "front": "晩",
        "back": "늦을 만"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 7",
        "front": "覺",
        "back": "깨달을 각"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 8",
        "front": "範",
        "back": "법 범"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 9",
        "front": "珍",
        "back": "보배 진"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 10",
        "front": "首",
        "back": "머리 수"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 11",
        "front": "甲",
        "back": "갑옷 갑"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 12",
        "front": "遣",
        "back": "보낼 견"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 13",
        "front": "突",
        "back": "갑자기 돌"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 14",
        "front": "寧",
        "back": "편안할 녕(영)"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 15",
        "front": "牛",
        "back": "소 우"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 16",
        "front": "哀",
        "back": "슬플 애"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 17",
        "front": "慨",
        "back": "슬퍼할 개"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 18",
        "front": "屈",
        "back": "굽힐 굴"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 19",
        "front": "犬",
        "back": "개 견"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 20",
        "front": "暮",
        "back": "저물 모"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 21",
        "front": "由",
        "back": "말미암을 유"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 22",
        "front": "用",
        "back": "쓸 용"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 23",
        "front": "申",
        "back": "거듭 신"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 24",
        "front": "逸",
        "back": "편안할 일"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 25",
        "front": "閱",
        "back": "볼 열"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 26",
        "front": "亭",
        "back": "정자 정"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 27",
        "front": "血",
        "back": "피 혈"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 28",
        "front": "陷",
        "back": "빠질 함"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 29",
        "front": "沓",
        "back": "겹칠 답"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 30",
        "front": "那",
        "back": "어찌 나"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 31",
        "front": "納",
        "back": "들일 납"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 32",
        "front": "千",
        "back": "일천 천"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 33",
        "front": "年",
        "back": "해 년"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 34",
        "front": "于",
        "back": "어조사 우"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 35",
        "front": "畏",
        "back": "두려워할 외"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 36",
        "front": "衣",
        "back": "옷 의"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 37",
        "front": "衷",
        "back": "속마음 충"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 38",
        "front": "悔",
        "back": "뉘우칠 회"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 39",
        "front": "惟",
        "back": "생각할 유"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 40",
        "front": "恒",
        "back": "항상 항"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 41",
        "front": "愚",
        "back": "어리석을 우"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 42",
        "front": "述",
        "back": "펼 술"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 43",
        "front": "醉",
        "back": "취할 취"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 44",
        "front": "太",
        "back": "클 태"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 45",
        "front": "幕",
        "back": "장막 막"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 46",
        "front": "漠",
        "back": "넓을 막"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 47",
        "front": "膜",
        "back": "꺼풀 막"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 48",
        "front": "卷",
        "back": "책 권"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 49",
        "front": "泰",
        "back": "클 태"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 50",
        "front": "在",
        "back": "있을 재"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 51",
        "front": "坐",
        "back": "앉을 좌"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 52",
        "front": "修",
        "back": "닦을 수"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 53",
        "front": "守",
        "back": "지킬 수"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 54",
        "front": "致",
        "back": "이를 치"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 55",
        "front": "網",
        "back": "그물 망"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 56",
        "front": "孝",
        "back": "효도 효"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 57",
        "front": "郊",
        "back": "둘 교"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 58",
        "front": "量",
        "back": "헤아릴 량(양)"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 59",
        "front": "良",
        "back": "어질 량(양)"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 60",
        "front": "尾",
        "back": "꼬리 미"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 61",
        "front": "眠",
        "back": "잘 면"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 62",
        "front": "筆",
        "back": "붓 필"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 63",
        "front": "獲",
        "back": "얻을 획"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 64",
        "front": "草",
        "back": "풀 초"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 65",
        "front": "忍",
        "back": "참을 인"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 66",
        "front": "半",
        "back": "반 반"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 67",
        "front": "迷",
        "back": "미혹할 미"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 68",
        "front": "勸",
        "back": "권할 권"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 69",
        "front": "歡",
        "back": "기쁠 환"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 70",
        "front": "秦",
        "back": "성씨 진"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 71",
        "front": "辛",
        "back": "매울 신"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 72",
        "front": "災",
        "back": "재앙 재"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 73",
        "front": "罪",
        "back": "허물 죄"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 74",
        "front": "宇",
        "back": "집 우"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 75",
        "front": "宙",
        "back": "집 주"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 76",
        "front": "宅",
        "back": "댁 댁"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 77",
        "front": "伸",
        "back": "펼 신"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 78",
        "front": "橫",
        "back": "가로 횡"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 79",
        "front": "置",
        "back": "둘 치"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 80",
        "front": "路",
        "back": "길 로"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 81",
        "front": "資",
        "back": "재물 자"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 82",
        "front": "效",
        "back": "본받을 효"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 83",
        "front": "埋",
        "back": "묻을 매"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 84",
        "front": "僅",
        "back": "겨우 근"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 85",
        "front": "旦",
        "back": "아침 단"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 86",
        "front": "麥",
        "back": "보리 맥"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 87",
        "front": "侮",
        "back": "업신여길 모"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 88",
        "front": "美",
        "back": "아름다울 미"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 89",
        "front": "匹",
        "back": "짝 필"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 90",
        "front": "品",
        "back": "물건 품"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 91",
        "front": "得",
        "back": "얻을 득"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 92",
        "front": "早",
        "back": "이를 조"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 93",
        "front": "初",
        "back": "처음 초"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 94",
        "front": "洋",
        "back": "큰 바다 양"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 95",
        "front": "連",
        "back": "잇다을 연"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 96",
        "front": "邊",
        "back": "가 변"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 97",
        "front": "返",
        "back": "돌이킬 반"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 98",
        "front": "雨",
        "back": "비 우"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 99",
        "front": "登",
        "back": "오를 등"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 100",
        "front": "受",
        "back": "받을 수"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 101",
        "front": "臥",
        "back": "누울 와"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 102",
        "front": "父",
        "back": "아버지 부"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 103",
        "front": "央",
        "back": "가운데 앙"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 104",
        "front": "殺",
        "back": "죽일 살"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 105",
        "front": "悲",
        "back": "슬플 비"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 106",
        "front": "鹿",
        "back": "사슴 록"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 107",
        "front": "米",
        "back": "쌀 미"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 108",
        "front": "金",
        "back": "쇠 금"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 109",
        "front": "秋",
        "back": "가을 추"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 110",
        "front": "鼻",
        "back": "코 비"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 111",
        "front": "驚",
        "back": "놀랄 경"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 112",
        "front": "留",
        "back": "머무를 류(유)"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 113",
        "front": "聽",
        "back": "들을 청"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 114",
        "front": "散",
        "back": "흩을 산"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 115",
        "front": "藏",
        "back": "감출 장"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 116",
        "front": "分類",
        "back": "분류"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 117",
        "front": "空氣",
        "back": "공기"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 118",
        "front": "同時多發",
        "back": "동시다발"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 119",
        "front": "空間的",
        "back": "공간적"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 120",
        "front": "上司",
        "back": "상사"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 121",
        "front": "後輩",
        "back": "후배"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 122",
        "front": "引導",
        "back": "인도"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 123",
        "front": "態度",
        "back": "태도"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 124",
        "front": "主體",
        "back": "주체"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 125",
        "front": "展開",
        "back": "전개"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 126",
        "front": "盲目的",
        "back": "주관이나 원칙이 없이 덮어놓고 행동하는"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 127",
        "front": "復古",
        "back": "복고"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 128",
        "front": "復興",
        "back": "부흥"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 129",
        "front": "自身",
        "back": "자신"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 130",
        "front": "訓鍊",
        "back": "훈련"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 131",
        "front": "基本",
        "back": "기본"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 132",
        "front": "基",
        "back": "터 기"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 133",
        "front": "廣",
        "back": "넓을 광"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 134",
        "front": "奪還",
        "back": "탈환"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 135",
        "front": "賤民",
        "back": "천민"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 136",
        "front": "頭腦",
        "back": "두뇌"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 137",
        "front": "貴族",
        "back": "귀족"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 138",
        "front": "默默不答",
        "back": "아무런 대답도 없이"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 139",
        "front": "加速",
        "back": "속도를 덧붙일"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 140",
        "front": "苦悶",
        "back": "고민"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 141",
        "front": "投票率",
        "back": "투표율"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 142",
        "front": "信賴",
        "back": "신뢰"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 143",
        "front": "政黨",
        "back": "정당"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 144",
        "front": "正當性",
        "back": "정당성"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 145",
        "front": "背山臨水",
        "back": "배산임수"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 146",
        "front": "作用",
        "back": "작용"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 147",
        "front": "急",
        "back": "급할 급"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 148",
        "front": "緩",
        "back": "느릴 완"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 149",
        "front": "接合",
        "back": "접합"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 150",
        "front": "塵",
        "back": "티끌 진"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 151",
        "front": "志操",
        "back": "지조"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 152",
        "front": "信念",
        "back": "신념"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 153",
        "front": "苦痛",
        "back": "괴로움 (고통)"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 154",
        "front": "評價",
        "back": "평가"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 155",
        "front": "價",
        "back": "값 가"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 156",
        "front": "許諾",
        "back": "허락"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 157",
        "front": "尊敬",
        "back": "존경"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 158",
        "front": "感謝",
        "back": "감사"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 159",
        "front": "健康",
        "back": "건강"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 160",
        "front": "國籍",
        "back": "국적"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 161",
        "front": "情報",
        "back": "정보"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 162",
        "front": "適用",
        "back": "적용"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 163",
        "front": "遂行",
        "back": "수행"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 164",
        "front": "經營戰略",
        "back": "경영전략"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 165",
        "front": "理解",
        "back": "이해"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 166",
        "front": "利用",
        "back": "이용"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 167",
        "front": "條件",
        "back": "조건"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 168",
        "front": "決",
        "back": "결단할 결 (결코)"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 169",
        "front": "趣向",
        "back": "취향"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 170",
        "front": "透明",
        "back": "투명"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 171",
        "front": "生活",
        "back": "생활"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 172",
        "front": "人物",
        "back": "인물"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 173",
        "front": "敎化",
        "back": "교화"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 174",
        "front": "兄弟",
        "back": "형제"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv50 - 175",
        "front": "必要",
        "back": "필요"
    }
]